<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></description>
        <link>http://gigabitcoin.xyz/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:21:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://gigabitcoin.xyz/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethereum (ETH) Monthly Price Trends]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ethereum (ETH) Monthly Price Trends</h1><p>During the last couple of months Ethereum was undergoing correction towards its long-term trend. That rebound can very well be considered finished. There was no turn in the long-term scope. Ethereum's price has failed to break through a number of key long-term resistances, which would allow it to form a turn.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b4dcf052da7522cb594fa0ffa376a2ca39538d02.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://cointelegraph.com/news/ethereum-eth-monthly-price-trends</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a41054bf-ca86-434a-a198-414c787c22cb</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:18:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chain to Showcase Blockchain Standard at Consensus 2016 Conference in New York]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Chain to Showcase Blockchain Standard at Consensus 2016 Conference in New York</h1><p>San Francisco-based Chain, Inc., a blockchain developer company, announced the release of their Open Chain Standard 1 (Chain OS 1) blockchain protocol, which has been in development for the last 18 months. Chain developed the new protocol with the assistance of several financial firms: Capital One, Citigroup, Fidelity, First Data, Fiserv, MUFG, Nasdaq, State Street and Visa.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2557cff977991410052a156e124c185f448b9959.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/chain-to-showcase-blockchain-standard-at-consensus-2016-conference-in-new-york/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4026ba8e-aeb6-409b-8b97-f1203d0d9d9f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:18:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Former Maestro CEO Joins Agentic Group Blockchain Consortium]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Former Maestro CEO Joins Agentic Group Blockchain Consortium</h1><p>Blockchain consortia are nothing new under the sun these days, and Agentic Group is one of one consortium very few people have heard of so far. This global Blockchain and digital currency initiative has added former Maestro CEO Ann Camarillo to their Senior Advisors board.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/b411a11372aa0b1dc961ba4a882767cc798e4cd4.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bitcoinist.net/former-maestro-ceo-joins-agentic-group-blockchain-consortium/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7bec48ab-3b8a-40d6-bc37-fb1a7d43a61c</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:18:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Claymore's Dual Ethereum and Decred GPU Miner Linux Binary]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Claymore's Dual Ethereum and Decred GPU Miner Linux Binary</h1><p>Claymore has released a Linux binary of his Dual Ethereum and Decred GPU miner for AMD GPUs. Prior to that the dual miner was only available for Windows users, but now Linux miners can also try to run it and increase their mining profit by mining ETH and DCR at the same time.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a008e58415e772458e44b15580b695b76ed67fa1.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://cryptomining-blog.com/7810-claymores-dual-ethereum-and-decred-gpu-miner-linux-binary/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e6255e9f-989d-4464-810c-b5221b159e56</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:18:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[China Joins the Blockchain Race With ChinaLedger Alliance]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>China Joins the Blockchain Race With ChinaLedger Alliance</h1><p>Wanxiang Blockchain Labs, a Shanghai-based nonprofit research institution which hosted the first Global Blockchain Summit in Shanghai, is to lead an alliance of 11 regional commodity exchanges, equity exchanges and financial asset exchanges with the aim of creating "an open source blockchain protocol that developers can further build upon in the future" according to Bai Shuo, former chief engineer of the Shanghai Stock Exchange and director of the technology committee for the ChinaLedger Alliance.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/7424a171763b04d72d880c6d8c5f9333b255bcfb.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/china-joins-the-blockchain-race-with-chinaledger-alliance-1462204569</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">73287a07-c0b2-440f-bd78-7c8d0d34f40e</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:18:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Industry Heavy Hitters Reveal the 'Real Satoshi' - Bitcoin News]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Industry Heavy Hitters Reveal the 'Real Satoshi' - Bitcoin News</h1><p>Well, it's never a dull day in Also read: Gavin Andresen Resumes Work on Bitcoin Core Bitcoin-land , to say the least. Hours ago John Matonis tweeted to the public and revealed a blog called drcraigwright.net revealing a PGP signature from Dr. Craig Wright claiming to be the real Satoshi Nakamoto.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c8aeb426f6a27d648930014484964a8fc627f8d3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://news.bitcoin.com/heavy-hitters-reveal-real-satoshi/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1438aee1-d779-4130-9b00-a433798ab723</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:18:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skepticism Abound: Community Wary of Craig Wright Satoshi Claims]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Skepticism Abound: Community Wary of Craig Wright Satoshi Claims</h1><p>Bitcoin community sleuths are already attempting to debunk the reported proof that Dr. Craig Wright is the creator of Bitcoin, the face behind the Satoshi Nakamoto moniker. Also read: New Ransomware Strains No Longer Want Your Bitcoin Early this morning the BBC published a report about Dr. Wright, which claimed that he provided "technical proof" of his Bitcoin creator identity.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8b2a15454b799e2f30132d7785d5f1d43b6a1808.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bitcoinist.net/community-wary-craig-wright/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">aba14321-1542-44f0-a8dd-f8d06d0d9551</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:18:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can Craig Steven Wright Prove He Is Bitcoin Creator Satoshi Nakamoto?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Can Craig Steven Wright Prove He Is Bitcoin Creator Satoshi Nakamoto?</h1><p>Determining the identity of Satoshi Nakamoto isn't as simple as solving the paternity of a brilliant child, in which a DNA test would solve the issue quickly. Bitcoin, from its foundation, has never been so simple. Craig Steven Wright, a 45-year-old Australian inventor and computer scientist, now claims he, in fact, is Nakamoto after denying it in December when he was first " outed."</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/aedffd4ad05778a2b726c6d3ebc2538efbd53f05.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/can-craig-steven-wright-prove-bitcoin-satoshi-nakamoto/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f57173ed-81ef-409c-9d48-9a184e5fe46e</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:18:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CME Group Collaborates with Crypto Facilities to Build Bitcoin Products - NEWSBTC]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>CME Group Collaborates with Crypto Facilities to Build Bitcoin Products - NEWSBTC</h1><p>CME Group has announced that it will be developing new products in collaboration with Crypto Facilities Limited to help the bitcoin trading community. Read more... CME Group, the world's leading derivatives marketplace has now collaborated with Crypto Facilities Limited, a London-based bitcoin financial services firm to develop new cryptocurrency based products.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3ae7a112ef752faa22acf5c83c1495ce8e1d32e4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/05/02/cme-group-collaborates-crypto-finance-build-new-products/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3dc8fa4a-c215-4207-b684-b6d067e5f17c</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:18:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BTC Relay Brings Bitcoin to Ethereum Smart Contracts On The Mainnet]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>BTC Relay Brings Bitcoin to Ethereum Smart Contracts On The Mainnet</h1><p>Over the past few months, there has been a fair amount of discussion as to whether or not Bitcoin and Ethereum are direct competitors. While people were still trying to figure out which side of the fence they were on, several developers have created BTC Relay, which bridges the gap between the Bitcoin blockchain and Ethereum smart contracts.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9d538883db8d829c7c664b3f694960562f2b05eb.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/btc-relay-brings-bitcoin-to-ethereum-smart-contracts-on-the-mainnet/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0f4c5ac7-56b3-4e56-9e93-993afe92779a</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 02:18:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>