<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></description>
        <link>http://gigabitcoin.xyz/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://gigabitcoin.xyz/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Foundation Has a Few Months Left, Recent Gift Not Enough]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bitcoin Foundation Has a Few Months Left, Recent Gift Not Enough</h1><p>A recent Bitcoin Foundation Board of Directors meeting revealed that the organization is on the ropes, with only a few months worth of funding left Also read: Russia's National Cryptocurrency Would Ban Rivals . This news comes after a $55-65 thousand dollar donation Brock Pierce secured from the BitClub mining organization.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/bd07977aa6506ccbd94be9877be8786ca3e2f833.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-foundation-gift-still-not-enough/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">eb6958a1-357e-49ad-9d3b-e875627ef701</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compact Blocks FAQ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Compact Blocks FAQ</h1><p>Compact block relay, BIP152, is a method of reducing the amount of bandwidth used to propagate new blocks to full nodes. Using simple techniques it is possible to reduce the amount of bandwidth necessary to propagate new blocks to full nodes when they already share much of the same mempool contents.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoincore.org/en/2016/06/07/compact-blocks-faq/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">aa972e0d-60d5-4dff-8438-b7e6b2fa8abc</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Egnyte Protects Companies From Local and Cloud-based Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Egnyte Protects Companies From Local and Cloud-based Ransomware Attacks</h1><p>Stopping the number of ransomware attacks and data breaches should be the top priority for every enterprise in existence. Egnyte Protect is on the right track, as they offer a brand new service which provides access control and blocks harmful software at the same time.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/52421094438352ca32b2fe9ffe8492ac2dca6efe.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/egnyte-protects-companies-from-local-and-cloud-based-ransomware-attacks/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8ffa98ae-8b34-4232-b8c5-916ed7efac3d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Boardroom Broadcasted Its First Bitcoin Transaction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Federal Reserve Boardroom Broadcasted Its First Bitcoin Transaction</h1><p>Hardly anyone will be surprised the regulatory engagement in the blockchain world is reaching new highs. Hardly anyone ever expected to use the terms Federal Reserve and Bitcoin in the same sentence in a positive manner. As it turns out, the Fed has been quite open to Bitcoin and blockchain as of late, but there is still a lot of work to be done.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a815e7bb9635d6c0f53f738a51011103efbb3cc7.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/06/07/federal-reserve-boardroom-broadcasted-first-bitcoin-transaction/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">83477d77-f2f2-43e3-95d6-a9b7b2640567</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prison Librarian Purchased Firearm and Cocaine From Deep Web]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Prison Librarian Purchased Firearm and Cocaine From Deep Web</h1><p>The deep web appeals to people from all walks of life, including a prison librarian at HMP Brixton. After ordering a Glock 19 handgun and ammunition from a darknet marketplace, he wanted to have the goods delivered to his home. That same address was also used for his drug dealing operation.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f933b7bbd75350216070dfd17eb02cf99d4a0c93.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/prison-librarian-purchased-firearm-and-cocaine-from-deep-web/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ef5c9fd8-50b7-4a8c-9bbf-fa54c127e192</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The $1.7 Trillion Reason Banks Prefer Blockchain or Distributed Ledger Over Bitcoin]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The $1.7 Trillion Reason Banks Prefer Blockchain or Distributed Ledger Over Bitcoin</h1><p>Banks know Blockchain is a threat to the linchpin of their economics: the customer relationship, and the $1.7 trillion they made in 2014 from global payments revenue which is a massive 40% of their annual profits. Historically the banking industry has provided three main services: financing, investment and transactions.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/f72d6ce96705994b06e905c379d339946b2f2ccf.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://cointelegraph.com/news/the-17-trillion-reason-banks-prefer-blockchain-or-distributed-ledger-over-bitcoin</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3beac549-2e13-43ef-92ed-8bdead3a2a68</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Winklevoss Twins: Bitcoin is Better at Being Gold Than Gold]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Winklevoss Twins: Bitcoin is Better at Being Gold Than Gold</h1><p>In a televised interview, the Winklevoss Twins state that bitcoin is more stable than gold as a store of value, opining that investors are starting to look at storing their wealth in the cryptocurrency. The Winklevoss Twins are understandably going through a press-tour, plugging their Gemini exchange which began operations in Canada yesterday.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/1705e05558721fa60375c909f155676fc2fc7432.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/winklevoss-twins-bitcoin-better-gold-gold/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7b5caf98-caa6-4839-9d5c-031fced4f7b1</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bloomberg Editorial Board: Public and Private Blockchains Need Level Playing Field - CoinDesk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bloomberg Editorial Board: Public and Private Blockchains Need Level Playing Field - CoinDesk</h1><p>The editorial board for Bloomberg News has called for a permissive regulatory environment for blockchain development, particularly in the area of public versions of the technology such as bitcoin. In an editorial published yesterday, the board advocated for the use of so-called regulatory sandboxes, or rule-making frameworks that allow companies to test financial products within a limited scope and customer range.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/91af0ddc1cf2f64064a56cda4ac1d0025c9fffd6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coindesk.com/bloomberg-editorial-blockchain/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cc91c48c-0862-4c67-b1d8-99c68b6d0afd</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Fluent Wants to Streamline Financial Supply Chains With a Blockchain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How Fluent Wants to Streamline Financial Supply Chains With a Blockchain</h1><p>As blockchain fever is taking hold of prominent financial industry firms around the globe, two men from Kentucky believe to have found the key to rewire international supply chain infrastructure. Fluent cofounders Lamar Wilson (CEO and developer) and Lafe Taylor (CDO) recently unveiled the Fluent Network, a blockchain-based financial operating network to streamline supply chain finance.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/802038e5360da0a74eae474ccd0591701c6512de.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/how-fluent-wants-to-streamline-financial-supply-chains-with-a-blockchain-1465318410</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">43dce936-b3e2-4e6f-b30a-1e6af0258965</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Airbitz and Augur partner in virtual trading predictions]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Airbitz and Augur partner in virtual trading predictions</h1><p>San Diego based Airbitz Inc., a leading blockchain, and data security-company, recently announced a partnership with Augur, a decentralized Ethereum-based prediction market. Do you think Hillary Clinton will win the presidency in November? Here is how Augur's market works. The purchase price of a share is $1.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c8d95308d50e6680524713d25d1990983ea086e5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bravenewcoin.com/news/airbitz-and-augur-partner-in-virtual-trading-predictions/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a5f40e79-4be8-4f65-acf0-8ebe578a6214</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 19:25:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>