<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></description>
        <link>http://gigabitcoin.xyz/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:18:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://gigabitcoin.xyz/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vaultoro Celebrates Anniversary With 50% Trading Discount]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Vaultoro Celebrates Anniversary With 50% Trading Discount</h1><p>Vaultoro is celebrating their anniversary today, and platform customers can enjoy a 50% trading fee reduction for the next month. Trading between gold and bitcoin at discounted prices is always a bonus and an excellent way to celebrate this company's service. Also read: Will the Bitcoin Price Hang Where It Is for a Little While?</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8d84e9ccd39d417e4d4b1ff255b6cd972fb63b30.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bitcoinist.net/vaultoro-celebrates-anniversary-trading-discount/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">05573d5a-2ba9-4fc8-9460-7a55b280de94</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coinbase Co-Founder Ehrsam: Bitcoin's Open Network Beats Private Blockchains]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Coinbase Co-Founder Ehrsam: Bitcoin's Open Network Beats Private Blockchains</h1><p>Fred Ehrsam, co-founder of Coinbase, noted in a Yahoo video interview that while the present period is a great time for bitcoin, controversy also surrounds bitcoin and blockchain technology. Asked by Yahoo finance reporter Dan Roberts about the interest in blockchain technology that is overshadowing bitcoin, Ehrsam compared the debate to the dawn of the Internet when closed corporate Intranets were common.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0ac9b1bdb039a8022f05db1a0bfc50eebf9fd97b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/coinbase-co-founder-ehrsam-bitcoins-open-network-beats-private-blockchains/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cd5dce90-4518-4c95-a3d5-13fd4d11139b</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulations Force Uber, Lyft out of Austin, Arcade City Moves In]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Regulations Force Uber, Lyft out of Austin, Arcade City Moves In</h1><p>Ride-sharing companies Uber and Lyft have ceased operations in the city of Austin, Texas due to government regulations. Arcade City, decentralized ride-sharing company, has commenced operations in Austin to fill the void left by the two outgoing ridesharing companies. The city of Austin passed an ordinance requiring more stringent background checks, including fingerprinting, for ridesharing.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e91becf1be8df2323418f241a09cbc231ecfa5ce.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://cointelegraph.com/news/regulations-force-uber-lyft-out-of-austin-arcade-city-moves-in</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bf92c5bb-5eeb-402d-be69-e5061c50370f</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Core Threatens a Hard Fork over Asicboost Mining Optimization]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bitcoin Core Threatens a Hard Fork over Asicboost Mining Optimization</h1><p>Peter Todd, backed by Matt Corallo, has proposed hard-fork changes to the bitcoin network to make "useless" patent pending algorithmic improvements which give mining an Asicboost of 20%, leading to increased profits of some $30 million if used by one of the biggest mining pools.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/16faaef4f8c42d3982905ed624f50b1ab7c24828.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/bitcoin-core-threatens-hard-fork-asicboost-mining-optimization/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">afe1e73b-6642-4bdf-822d-52f612f9441f</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blockchain and the Race Towards Irrelevance - CoinDesk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Blockchain and the Race Towards Irrelevance - CoinDesk</h1><p>Matthew Spoke is a bitcoin and Ethereum enthusiast who has been working towards advancing the use of smart distributed protocols through Rubix, a team at Deloitte dedicated to this vision. In this opinion piece, Spoke argues it remains to be seen whether blockchain can be a disruptive or complementary technology, even while many incumbents are investing on the belief it's the latter.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/1d6bce4e7544977d8b480a6c4d2832a085eee11f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coindesk.com/race-toward-irrelevance/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fc33039f-dd35-4813-8d93-92b60dfdfcf8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Myths Mainstream Media Gets Wrong Every Time]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Bitcoin Myths Mainstream Media Gets Wrong Every Time</h1><p>The privacy issues associated with Bitcoin make it unsuitable for any illegal purpose in general. For several years now, there seem to be a lot of myths surrounding Bitcoin which need to be clarified and rectified. Several of these topics keep returning on a regular basis, showing an apparent lack of education as far as mainstream media is concerned.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/2d43793c5102d518cd97458b360f794c0dd393e9.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/05/15/bitcoin-myths-mainstream-media-gets-wrong-every-time/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8a806b6b-ae77-4c94-87bf-b75c5db78af2</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:17:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coinizy Exits Beta Phase and Launches Ethereum Debit Card]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Coinizy Exits Beta Phase and Launches Ethereum Debit Card</h1><p>Up until now, there has hardly been any talk about issuing a debit card cryptocurrency users can fund with Ethereum. Bitcoin debit cards are becoming very common, and Coinizy is the first company to launch and Ethereum debit card.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/c6ad5420bb10bf3f62cb3f22c6d5b709dc67f3b5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/coinizy-exits-beta-phase-and-launches-ethereum-debit-card/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e18fd51b-7e49-42eb-9d23-ccf00e081719</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wright Was Right, Even If He's Wrong: Satoshi Should Never Be Revealed]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Wright Was Right, Even If He's Wrong: Satoshi Should Never Be Revealed</h1><p>The dust has finally cleared around Craig Wright's public claim that he was Satoshi Nakamoto, Bitcoin's enigmatic creator. After publicly coming out and presenting evidence to the media, this was quickly dismissed as dubiously insufficient proof. Wright then promised to provide irrefutable proof by moving some of the first Bitcoin ever mined, which was met with much doubt and derision.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/edc0382bbbcaefd6df45661a8cef56dcade04830.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://cointelegraph.com/news/wright-was-right-even-if-hes-wrong-satoshi-should-never-be-revealed</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e183b2cd-bf1e-4396-88a4-8684310ff14c</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Anatomy of Bitcoin's Great Scaling Debate - CoinDesk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>An Anatomy of Bitcoin's Great Scaling Debate - CoinDesk</h1><p>Dr Paul Ennis is a research assistant at The Centre for Innovation, Technology & Organization at University College Dublin, specializing in bitcoin and blockchain studies. In this opinion piece, Dr Ennis discusses how bitcoin's scaling debate has thus far evolved, examining the various competing efforts, their processes and what the differences say about the developer community and its culture.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9b0d0992e89a57c1f6b77e3ad5d7ac0733ae0cee.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coindesk.com/anatomy-bitcoin-scaling-debate/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0539b2d6-94ea-4724-abdf-8aeb40c3f368</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlimited Warrantless Searches For The FBI Are On The Horizon]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Unlimited Warrantless Searches For The FBI Are On The Horizon</h1><p>Not too long ago, we reported how the FBI will soon be able to get a warrant to hack any computer with anonymity software, regardless of what this software is being used for. But that is not the only cause of concern, as the number of warrantless searches is growing month over month.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/687bee79a9957d6bb68a39ca850b63e3ee55e79c.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/unlimited-warrantless-searches-for-the-fbi-are-on-the-horizon/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f8fc3da0-aa06-4c59-ab86-c5388ed06498</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 16:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>