<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></description>
        <link>http://gigabitcoin.xyz/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:32:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://gigabitcoin.xyz/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin.com Launches a High-Stakes Casino - Bitcoin News]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bitcoin.com Launches a High-Stakes Casino - Bitcoin News</h1><p>Bitcoin.com Also read: Bitstamp Moves to Luxembourg, Becomes First Nationally-Licensed Exchange is excited to announce a new casino portal added to our page, and a new partnership with gaming provider SoftSwiss . Casino.bitcoin.com will feature over 1,000 games from a wide array of gaming platforms, which fall under the purview of the SoftSwiss gaming license, based in Curaçao.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/9c1eb30a26eff440839ac948bcdf018631fb2aae.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://news.bitcoin.com/bitcoin-com-launches-casino/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">52162868-bf70-4e8d-bf72-97035b5af9d0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:28:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Reaches a Crossroads With the Scaling Debate, Not a Crisis]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bitcoin Reaches a Crossroads With the Scaling Debate, Not a Crisis</h1><p>Judging from various reports in the media over the past year, Bitcoin is in a serious crisis that threatens its very existence. Longtime Bitcoin developer Mike Hearn even left the ecosystem entirely and claimed the project is now a failed experiment. Of course, Bitcoin has been proclaimed dead roughly 100 other times.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e68ed5ef9ce3d536e3fd5c54139986a245bc6dc5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/bitcoin-reaches-a-crossroads-with-the-scaling-debate-not-a-crisis-1462980183</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bd06ee5c-7c50-4e48-a2ca-f9d513591efe</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:28:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The latest customers for the technology behind bitcoin are NATO and the US military]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The latest customers for the technology behind bitcoin are NATO and the US military</h1><p>Blockchain technology, the backbone of bitcoin, has a lot of applications. Finance firms want to use to cut down on administrative costs and trade faster. Estonia is using to securely track health records. Now it's the military's turn. Both the US Department of Defense (DoD) and NATO have put out requests for military-related apps built on blockchain, a decentralized...</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e572c48517da0f1585e6c5971db4a40f3112ae88.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://qz.com/681580/the-latest-customers-for-the-technology-behind-bitcoin-are-nato-and-the-us-military/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">561d1f3f-14ed-44f5-ac29-b18683fe439d</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:28:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OpenBazaar Celebrates 100,000 Downloads of Bitcoin-Powered Social Marketplace]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>OpenBazaar Celebrates 100,000 Downloads of Bitcoin-Powered Social Marketplace</h1><p>The distributed ecommerce platform OpenBazaar (OB) soft-launched in April and has received $1 million in venture funding from Andreessen Horowitz and Union Square Ventures. While the team admits "limitations" in the project's current state ‒ for instance, a store must run the OB client in order to appear online ‒ buyers and sellers are now free to come together and buy and sell goods for various forms of payment, including bitcoins.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0074058486d51d274d82e259d7204d6a6368f888.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoinmagazine.com/articles/openbazzar-celebrates-downloads-of-bitcoin-powered-social-marketplace-1462980995</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2ff5936c-173e-4916-afc9-cc190daf805e</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:28:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kraken Launches ETH Dark Pool Trading - Bitcoinist.net]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Kraken Launches ETH Dark Pool Trading - Bitcoinist.net</h1><p>The global Bitcoin and digital asset exchange Also read: Bitcoin is Back: Price Rises Nearly $15, Returns to $460 Kraken has announced it will be the first and only exchange enabling clients to use the (ETH) Dark Pool Trading. The Dark Pool allows users to "discreetly" place large trading orders without exposing the order book to the public.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/952fa8258f526d5efe17ce82aa0b4b46168f3287.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bitcoinist.net/kraken-eth-dark-pool-trading/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b7816381-d82d-426b-b5eb-8907fee0fc77</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:28:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bart Chilton: Bitcoin is a huge opportunity. Obama needs to make a move now]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bart Chilton: Bitcoin is a huge opportunity. Obama needs to make a move now</h1><p>Since the digital currency bitcoin and blockchain (the underlying technology) burst onto the scene in 2009, serious skepticism and palpable passion have played equal roles. Many bitcoin devotees wanted little to do with government legislators or regulators and regulators were dubious of this new currency.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e10a15d32be6e289173a6843203ab8dc52c19409.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.cnbc.com/2016/05/11/obama-needs-to-make-a-move-on-bitcoin-now-bart-chilton-commentary.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d11822d0-081d-41c3-9f25-078c90206aff</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:28:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bankruptcy Trustee Says MtGox Bitcoin Addresses Will Not Be Released]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bankruptcy Trustee Says MtGox Bitcoin Addresses Will Not Be Released</h1><p>Nobuaki Kobayashi, Bankruptcy Trustee for now-defunct Japanese bitcoin exchange MtGox, released a statement today saying that he will not release a list of bitcoin addresses supposedly controlled by MtGox, which he hoped would aid the investigation and recovery of missing customer funds.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/55e2199a70e3da37db934f19cdfb86ca93480b34.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/bankruptcy-trustee-says-mtgox-bitcoin-addresses-will-remain-private/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">202aed5c-9953-4bdd-9d84-772a61747c28</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:28:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ghana: First Comes Internet Security, Then Bitcoin]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ghana: First Comes Internet Security, Then Bitcoin</h1><p>Ghana seeks to secure transactions on the Internet first and only then start a discussion on Bitcoin adoption. As a lack of training on cryptography is still a major issue in parts of Africa, Ghana's Chapter of the Internet Society has trained some of its members.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ae578059f9118bb85c39a9ce0fd5c6b10d652533.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://cointelegraph.com/news/ghana-first-comes-internet-security-then-bitcoin</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a7aee2e1-023a-4260-a1e5-7deb8cf8b381</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:28:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blockchain Platform Fluent Raises $1.65m in Seed Fund]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Blockchain Platform Fluent Raises $1.65m in Seed Fund</h1><p>It is worth noting Fluent has been active in worlds of fintech and blockchain technology for a long time, which explains their vision of supporting disruptive companies with distributed ledger technology. Plenty of startups around the world are trying to leverage blockchain technology and bring it to different industries all over the world.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/82e2f956563fc2e30244e47db97fb70f88a2b100.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/05/11/blockchain-payment-platform-fluent-raises-1-65m-seed-fund/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c158cfd8-6595-46dd-9f00-2ee8ae8e77c1</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:28:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia Nearing Decision on Bitcoin Exchange Regulation - CoinDesk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Australia Nearing Decision on Bitcoin Exchange Regulation - CoinDesk</h1><p>The Australian government has officially responded to a Senate report in which lawmakers argued that the country should bring domestic digital currency exchanges under existing anti-money laundering (AML) and counter-terrorist financing (CTF) rules. In newly issued remarks, the Australian government indicated that it agrees with this recommendation and that it expects a review of the relevant laws to be released shortly.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/fb548c6f92ad5f7a1d81921b4000288f8845f890.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coindesk.com/australia-near-decision-bitcoin-exchange-aml-ctf/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5a15b0d8-ae0a-4e92-acd8-d5f90d070079</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 01:28:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>