<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></description>
        <link>http://gigabitcoin.xyz/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://gigabitcoin.xyz/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Retesting $680]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bitcoin Price Retesting $680</h1><p>The bitcoin price chart bubbles along just below $700 (Bitstamp) and mood in Bitcoin Land is positive. At the time of writing price is retesting the $680 (Bitstamp) level. This analysis is provided by xbt.social with a 3-hour delay. Read the full analysis here. Not a member?</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/d4c2a95778a39e494b741c0475b9cab48942b7d7.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.cryptocoinsnews.com/bitcoin-price-retesting-680/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">173e75eb-a742-4d21-a85b-64542ce69864</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Investment Vehicle Resumes Nasdaq Trading After Acquisition - CoinDesk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bitcoin Investment Vehicle Resumes Nasdaq Trading After Acquisition - CoinDesk</h1><p>A bitcoin trading option targeting European investors and listed on Nasdaq Nordic is once again live after the sudden bankruptcy of one of its principal backers. XBT Provider, the operator of Bitcoin Tracker One and Bitcoin Tracker EUR, announced today its acquisition by Global Advisors - a Jersey-based hedge fund specializing in digital currency.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6acfe53ac4449d6db1fe9df7d23edf3d8b063851.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coindesk.com/bitcoin-nasdaq-trading-xbt-provider/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d4d82004-0416-42b4-b4f3-189c94be6eba</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blockchain of Love: Someone Proposed Using Bitcoin]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Blockchain of Love: Someone Proposed Using Bitcoin</h1><p>The only thing more uncomfortable for friends and close relations than filming your marriage proposal and putting it online is being really, really into bitcoin. On Tuesday, somebody decided to go all-in on both of these modern horrors and became the latest person to propose using the bitcoin blockchain, the publicly viewable ledger that's stored on every bitcoin user's computer forever and ever.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a34d5d9cad1c4dbf5ab5366accf5d86c9d17d8b4.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://motherboard.vice.com/read/blockchain-of-love-someone-proposed-using-bitcoin</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f3379db5-aa74-41a4-baa5-f2cbed174077</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PwC to Study Blockchain Technology for Wholesale Insurance]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>PwC to Study Blockchain Technology for Wholesale Insurance</h1><p>PricewaterhouseCoopers Also read: Australian bitcoin exchanges announce Ethereum support (PwC), the largest professional services firm in the world, is set to initiate research into blockchain tech by focusing on its potential uses in wholesale insurance. The research will be a collaborative project between PwC and Z/Yen , a consultancy think-tank located in the City of London.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ccf737bd14066f0567715b59eba68d3907c11f0f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://news.bitcoin.com/pwc-study-blockchain-wholesale-insurance/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f9f7040b-8cdb-43c6-9756-0dd681b64164</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[P2P node support company, Node40, faces challenges in blockchain space]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>P2P node support company, Node40, faces challenges in blockchain space</h1><p>Sean Ryan and Perry Woodin are ideas men, and founders of Node40, an incentivized node service and Dash masternode hosting provider launched in 2015. "In the world of distributed Peer-to-Peer (P2P) decentralized blockchain applications, stability is of paramount importance. Without stable nodes, the network can experience issues," states the company site.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/34eba5d37797d04731a3a8541cf635b98946775f.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bravenewcoin.com/news/p2p-node-support-company-node40-faces-challenges-in-blockchain-space/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">54d9e769-37b6-4b5c-8629-3644569f25b2</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Japan will Release its Digital Currency in 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Japan will Release its Digital Currency in 2017</h1><p>This story points out how digital currency and cryptocurrency are not the same. It has been coming for quite some time now, but Japan is poised to be one of the first few countries issuing their own digital currency. With the Bitcoin value soaring as of late, the Bank of Tokyo-Mitsubishi will launch the currency as soon as Q3 2017.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/18c8a506fc695348c628897fb84fa3d2e2d9df44.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/06/14/japan-will-release-digital-currency-2017/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">08768339-f264-4af2-8d80-77b89ce4acc9</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Roger Ver is appointed as CEO of MGT Capital Investments]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Roger Ver is appointed as CEO of MGT Capital Investments</h1><p>According to recent reports, MGT Capital Investments, Inc. has decided to appoint Roger Ver, a popular member of the bitcoin community, as the Chairman of their Cryptocurrency Advisory Board. The appointment, which is effective immediately, is meant to ensure that the investment company keeps a close eye on the potential of digital currencies, while also facilitating the release of new products for their customers.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/bb681ddde6860463a3102b2c92f013ed1f09d2e6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/roger-ver-is-appointed-as-ceo-of-mgt-capital-investments/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f8a19abf-9cf9-445a-baba-b4c29a1a1a05</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[John McAfee leads cybersecurity company, signing up Roger Ver and Erik Voorhees]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>John McAfee leads cybersecurity company, signing up Roger Ver and Erik Voorhees</h1><p>Cybersecurity expert, libertarian presidential candidate, and founder of McAfee antivirus, John McAfee is taking over as CEO at publicly-traded MGT Capital Investments, Inc., (NYSE MKT: MGT). Fresh at the helm, McAfee is already charting a new course for the company, focusing on the how to secure cryptocurrencies.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/fa0c0ed2bef9f444981a9ae6227c28ba592c2796.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bravenewcoin.com/news/john-mcafee-leads-cybersecurity-company-signing-up-roger-ver-and-erik-vorhees/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">53340da3-4ebc-4bc6-b532-d89c7bbb14e4</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One Bitcoin is Worth 51 Million Hacked iMesh Accounts]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>One Bitcoin is Worth 51 Million Hacked iMesh Accounts</h1><p>People who have been using the Internet for quite some time now will recall the name iMesh, a once popular peer-to-peer file sharing platform. Although this platform has been defunct for some time, a hacker managed to obtain a database containing 51 million accounts.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a614d8ee51e5c91601c2f36db194db0a4b3aec30.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bitcoinist.net/one-bitcoin-worth-51-million-hacked-imesh-accounts/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">da411104-3518-4598-b8f9-4418158a79be</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jersey-based asset manager acquires Swedish issuer of bitcoin ETN]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Jersey-based asset manager acquires Swedish issuer of bitcoin ETN</h1><p>NEW YORK Asset management firm Global Advisors (Jersey) Limited said on Tuesday it has acquired XBT Provider, a Swedish publicly-listed company that launched the world's first bitcoin-backed exchange traded note. Global Advisors' co-founder Daniel Masters declined to disclose the terms of the acquisition, but said the company has taken over XBT's two ETN products called Bitcoin Tracker One and Bitcoin Tracker Euro.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/6e97add1cee49d9d0a7f087204eafc069359e468.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.reuters.com/article/us-bitcoin-acquisition-globaladvisors-idUSKCN0Z022T</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27352d1f-8490-4490-8212-72a1f542142f</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 17:35:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>