<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></description>
        <link>http://gigabitcoin.xyz/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:45:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://gigabitcoin.xyz/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IRC meeting summary for 2015-12-17]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>IRC meeting summary for 2015-12-17</h1><p>Replace-by-fee handling in wallets C++11 for 0.13 Currently when a node sees a transaction that spends the same output it ignores it. With RBF it replaces the current transaction in the mempool if it has a higher fee. This allows for things like spending "stuck" transactions, adding more recipients to a transaction in order to prevent chaining, etc.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoincore.org/en/meetings/2015/12/17/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a4a24a98-c11e-44fc-bc07-7d4186f95d89</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:40:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IRC meeting summary for 2015-12-10]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>IRC meeting summary for 2015-12-10</h1><p>BIP 68 Consensus-enforced transaction replacement signaled via sequence numbers , and current implementation. BIP 68 changes the meaning of the previously unused sequence number field to a relative locktime. When a block is created miners include a timestamp. This timestamp has to be between the median of the previous 11 blocks and the network-adjusted time +2 hours.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoincore.org/en/meetings/2015/12/10/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6536c2ff-a471-4869-9e1b-f906dbecc744</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:40:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IRC meeting summary for 2015-11-26]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>IRC meeting summary for 2015-11-26</h1><p>CLTV activation BIP68/BIP112 implementation Replace-by-fee CheckLockTimeVerify (CLTV) aka "how you thought nLockTime worked before you actually tried to use it" aka OP_HODL. It's plausible the CLTV softfork will activate within just a few weeks, as everyone but a few big miners have adopted it. About 20% of the nodes currently run CLTV-supporting versions.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoincore.org/en/meetings/2015/11/26/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9bab72d5-e62d-4cd9-b8ce-a35167955832</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:40:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IRC meeting summary for 2015-11-05]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>IRC meeting summary for 2015-11-05</h1><p>Sigcache performance Performance goals for 0.12 transaction priority sigops flooding attack chain limits Note: cfields, mcelrath and BlueMatt (and maybe more) missed the meeting because of daylight saving time. Closing date for proposals for the scaling bitcoin workshop is the 9th. Check to see if there are any other commits for the 0.11.2 RC.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoincore.org/en/meetings/2015/11/05/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5e9ba45b-13a1-46ea-a7d1-2ba358803b1c</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:40:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IRC meeting summary for 2015-12-03]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>IRC meeting summary for 2015-12-03</h1><p>BIP68-related pull requests Eviction and onions BIP for opt-in RBF A lot of developers where traveling to the scaling bitcoin conference ( videos), so this is again a shorter, and it'll likely be the same next week (as a lot of developers stay in Hong Kong for the developer meetup after the conference).</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoincore.org/en/meetings/2015/12/03/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dbdb7ef4-9d25-4eea-8e36-826af666bf4a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:40:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IRC meeting summary for 2015-10-29]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>IRC meeting summary for 2015-10-29</h1><p>Upcoming softfork Chain limits Clang format BIP68 and BIP112 implementations The LevelDB topic was started but deferred till after the meeting as there are currently no plans to move to another database. However research and testing is encouraged. mcelrath volunteered to make a LMDB branch, jgarzik already has a sqlite branch.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoincore.org/en/meetings/2015/10/29/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2217ecdb-5a57-4b6b-a75e-83227ab9b301</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:40:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IRC meeting summary for 2015-10-08]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>IRC meeting summary for 2015-10-08</h1><p>Mempool limiting: chain limits Low-S change CLTV & CSV review Creation of bitcoin discuss mailing list This issue has made most JS bitcoin software vulnerable to generating incorrect public keys. "This is an ecosystem threat with the potential to cause millions of dollars in losses that needs higher visibility; though it's not a bitcoin core / bitcoin network issue.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoincore.org/en/meetings/2015/10/08/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6d933d93-9daa-40c1-b4e3-0c312deb58b9</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:40:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Site Design, New Order Options]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>New Site Design, New Order Options</h1><p>Since Gemini launched, we've deepened our understanding of what you all want to see on our website and how we can best provide you with relevant information. We want your interaction with Gemini to be as efficient and user-friendly as possible - this goes back to our core principle of giving you what you need, when you need it .</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/49574636909e0023fc6f7e869ea949fdd5a030d1.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://gemini.com/blog/new-design-new-order-options/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fca12121-37c7-4865-887a-96d9a9a92846</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:40:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IRC meeting summary for 2015-10-01]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>IRC meeting summary for 2015-10-01</h1><p>The full IRC-logs can be found here. Mempool limiting BIP68 + CHECKSEQUENCEVERIFY CLTV soft fork deployment libconsensus merge time window When a transaction is relayed across the network it is held by the nodes in memory, until it gets into a block. All these transactions that sit in memory are called the memorypool or mempool for short.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://bitcoincore.org/en/meetings/2015/10/01/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3ea8b507-17fd-4be3-8db7-7ee4c9e1aee6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:40:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SXSW Promotion: Free Bitcoin for New Users!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>SXSW Promotion: Free Bitcoin for New Users!</h1><p>As part of a limited promotion, the first 500 USA-based new users that sign up to Gemini between Friday, March 11th (6:00pm EST) and Monday, March 14th (6:00pm EDT) will receive approximately $20 worth of bitcoin (0.05 BTC to be exact)! It's simple - sign up for an individual or institutional account, and complete the identity verification process.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4c1c6bd6359538eb4a1b1850edb1f93dce1b4263.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://gemini.com/blog/sxsw-promotion-free-bitcoin-for-new-users/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c2b396fd-89af-412d-800e-5635771f5660</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2016 13:40:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>