<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[big on bitcoin]]></description>
        <link>http://gigabitcoin.xyz/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 02:00:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://gigabitcoin.xyz/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The DAO, a List of Exchanges Where You Can Trade Tokens]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The DAO, a List of Exchanges Where You Can Trade Tokens</h1><p>The DAO, a decentralized autonomous organization, is an interesting project in the form of an Ethereum smart contract that is essentially a form of investor-directed venture capital fund. The project was started with what can be described as the largest crowdfunding campaign to date where over twenty thousand people invested over 12 million Ether coins and now have the right to control the direction of the DAO.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/47f9a4e40624c99239205a3ca3449ac027316f90.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://cryptomining-blog.com/7923-the-dao-a-list-of-exchanges-where-you-can-trade-tokens/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">44da9241-85e9-4d5b-b531-77f8db67d41c</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:59:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CFTC Fines Bitcoin Exchange Bitfinex $75,000 Over Trading Violations - CoinDesk]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>CFTC Fines Bitcoin Exchange Bitfinex $75,000 Over Trading Violations - CoinDesk</h1><p>Hong Kong-based bitcoin exchange Bitfinex has settled with the US Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) following an investigation into its financed trading activities. Bitfinex settled charges that it offered illegal off-exchange financed retail commodities trading, as well as not registering as a futures commission merchant.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/443f608726f4521d3ab31cb58f8d0288e0e96271.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.coindesk.com/cftc-bitcoin-exchange-bitfinex-trading-violations/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3444dbde-9e26-40ea-9389-6a5fe44492fc</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:59:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Egyptian Dentist Apprehended in Bitcoin Sting Operation in Cairo]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Egyptian Dentist Apprehended in Bitcoin Sting Operation in Cairo</h1><p>A 30-year-old dentist has been apprehended by Egyptian authorities for conducting bitcoin-to-dollar transactions on LocalBitcoins.com, a popular digital currency trading portal. Mr. Ahmed. A. H., who was trading digital currencies on the site under the nickname btc2okpay, was captured in a sting operation setup by investigators in New Cairo, a municipality on the outskirts of the Cairo.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/20d190049f9d6c65a9097af954e7d63f0057e735.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/egyptian-dentist-apprehended-in-bitcoin-sting-operation-in-cairo/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a601d96e-e8b0-4690-9243-f2c5c8d024c0</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:59:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PayPal Ban in Turkey May Open Doors for Bitcoin Businesses - NEWSBTC]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>PayPal Ban in Turkey May Open Doors for Bitcoin Businesses - NEWSBTC</h1><p>The exit of PayPal from the Turkey may pave way for new blockchain based digital payments systems Turkey might prove to be a gold mine for digital currencies companies in the coming days. Thanks to issues being faced by PayPal due to the Turkish government's refusal to renew their license to operate in the country.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3103834b5e76805bbe75d95359a46d71201fc348.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.newsbtc.com/2016/06/02/paypal-ban-in-turkey-may-open-doors-for-bitcoin-businesses/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">fcc4dce0-f199-467e-856d-9e8ee85eeaa6</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:59:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Currency Exchange Bitfinex to PAy 75k Fine to CFTC]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Digital Currency Exchange Bitfinex to PAy 75k Fine to CFTC</h1><p>Hong Kong-based digital currency exchange Bitfinex (BFXNA Inc.) will be paying a $75,000 fine to the United States Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC). According to the order, Bitfinex fully cooperated with CFTC investigators and submitted the 75k Offer of Settlement, which the CFTC has accepted.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a07eb1a24f1b274f5c0a5b6a55d4e8f6e02d21fb.gif"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/cftc-hits-digital-currency-exchange-bitfinex-with-75k-fine/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">91fbbe0c-847a-4336-a69e-c6a76bb1e4b1</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:59:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Like water access, Bitcoin can make finance a public utility]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Like water access, Bitcoin can make finance a public utility</h1><p>Developing nations are waking up to the opportunities that Bitcoin and open blockchain technology can provide to the world's poorest and financially excluded citizens, while banks appear to stifle their efforts and simultaneously develop their own privatized blockchain ledgers. Is it fair to explain private ledgers as another way to profit at the expense of a public utility?</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/86e9cd7fbe240d94a95f5d729a61e65a0d83bd70.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://news.bitcoin.com/banks-bitcoin-public-utility-money/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">70718456-a601-4233-98fe-47dd24faccfd</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:59:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DASH Price Remains Resilient Despite Lackluster Trading Volume]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>DASH Price Remains Resilient Despite Lackluster Trading Volume</h1><p>It has been a bit quiet on the DigitalCash front as of late, but don't be mistaken in thinking people lost interest in DASH all of a sudden. The cryptocurrency is still going strong to this very day, and there is plenty of volume to go around.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/01ba8431c8ded844a629c0280ddfa706aded6270.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://themerkle.com/dash-price-remains-resilient-despite-lackluster-trading-volume/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4432261d-f597-4d6d-b8d2-1652c85c83cb</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:59:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SovereignBTC #88 Putting First Things First and Bruce Fenton on Liberty, Investing, and Cryptocurrency]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>SovereignBTC #88 Putting First Things First and Bruce Fenton on Liberty, Investing, and Cryptocurrency</h1><p>In this edition of SovereignBTC, John Bush interviews Bruce Fenton about the state of cryptocurrency as well as his views on liberty and anarchism, controversy surrounding the Bitcoin Foundation, as well as his insights on bitcoin and a few altcoins. Before the interview, John continues his series covering Stephen Covey's Seven Habits of Highly Effective People.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4f8b407f5a6175618652c5a2609ec240b396f2e3.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://letstalkbitcoin.com/blog/post/sovereignbtc-88-putting-first-things-first-and-bruce-fenton-on-liberty-investing-and-cryptocurrency</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1162a5d8-81ec-49db-b3e9-8fed57f7fb70</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:59:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CTFC Levels 75,000 Dollar Fine at Bitfinex - Bitcoinist.net]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>CTFC Levels 75,000 Dollar Fine at Bitfinex - Bitcoinist.net</h1><p>The Commodity Futures Trading Commission Fined Bitfinex $75,000 today for "offering illegal off-exchange financed retail commodity transactions in bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies," citing the Commodity Exchange Act and Dodd-Frank for the action. This development may be the first of many to come if similar services, that host proxy wallets for the user, are found to be in violation of the same regulations.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a37c8c1025b4ebbaf571ae8dafeea71d38e6f2a0.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bitcoinist.net/ctfc-levels-75000-dollar-fine-at-bitfinex/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cc697666-1231-4b07-bf7e-4195c442df0e</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:59:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Visit to the Oracle]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A Visit to the Oracle</h1><p>Smart contracts are poised to revolutionize the ways that humans, machines, and organizations create and enforce contractual relationships. Everything from property ownership to financial instruments to family arrangements can now be implemented as a piece of code on a publicly verifiable shared ledger known as a blockchain.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/08148f90c240ff5b2f616f16d7a866d035502973.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bravenewcoin.com/news/a-visit-to-the-oracle/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b23fb60c-f841-4b6a-add0-fa7a24b46556</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:59:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>